{
    "subject": "resource/In_My_Chair",
    "predicate": "ontology/musicalArtist",
    "object": "resource/Status_Quo_(band)",
    "human_readable": "The musical artist behind 'In My Chair' is Status Quo (band).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9060768485069275,
            "question": "Is there a song called 'In My Chair' by Status Quo (band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8788354992866516,
            "question": "Who is the musical artist behind the song 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6909245848655701,
            "question": "Which song is associated with Status Quo (band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6574174165725708,
            "question": "Name a musical group known for the song 'In My Chair'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6230894923210144,
            "question": "What is the name of the band that performed 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.538593590259552,
            "question": "What song is Status Quo (band) famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5135323405265808,
            "question": "Who created the music for the song 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4756503701210022,
            "question": "Can you tell me the artist who sang 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4352216422557831,
            "question": "What band released the song 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41828879714012146,
            "question": "Who performed the song 'In My Chair'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The musical artist behind 'In My Chair' is Status Quo (band).",
            "html": "dbpedia_3832_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What band released the song 'In My Chair'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3832_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the artist who sang 'In My Chair'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3832_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who created the music for the song 'In My Chair'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3832_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3832_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3832_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3832_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3832_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3832_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3832_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3832_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3832_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3832_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3832_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided supports the triple. According to the documents, 'In My Chair' is a song by the English rock band Status Quo."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided clearly states that \"In My Chair\" is a song by the English rock band Status Quo. Therefore, the triple \"The musical artist behind 'In My Chair' is Status Quo (band)\" is correct according to the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}